Guide to the Richard C. Burns archive of Overtone Records, Inc.
Yale University Music Library
- Richard C. Burns recording projects, Series IV
  - Albertus Magnus Choir (OV-109), undated
    - Side B (Box 15, Item 81)
    - Reel 1 (Box 15, Item 82)
    - Reel 2 (Box 15, Item 83)
  - American Guild of Organists (AGO): Session 4, Dupré, 1973 May 27 (Box 15, Item 84)
  - American Guild of Organists (AGO): Session I and interviews, 1973 May 25–1973 May 26 (Box 15, Item 85)
  - American Guild of Organists (AGO), undated
    - Session 1 (Box 15, Item 86)
    - Session 2 (Box 15, Item 87)
    - Session 3 (Box 15, Item 88)
      Various works. Includes musical information in storage case.
  - American Guild of Organists Symposium: Sessions 2 and 3, 1973 May 26–1973 May 27 (Box 15, Item 89)
    Includes musical information in and on storage case.
  - Apostolic Christian Church Choir (OV-116), undated
    - Vol. I [?], circa 1966 (Box 15, Item 90)
      Includes musical information in storage case.
    - Vol. II, revised master, circa 1966 (Box 15, Item 91)
  - Bach, Johann Sebastian: Cantata BWC 4 and BWV 140, 1951 March 22 (Box 15, Item 92)
    Cantata BWV 4 [Christ lag in Todesbanden] and BWV 140 [Wachet auf, ruft uns die Stimme]; Choral Evensong for Maundy Thursday. St Thomas' Church. Includes musical information in storage case.
  - Bach, Johann Sebastian: Christmas Oratorio
    New Haven Chorale, Gustav Meier, conductor.
    - Reel 1, 1961 December 9 (Box 15, Item 93)
    - Reel 2, 1931 December 9 (Box 15, Item 94)
  - Bach, Johann Sebastian; Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart; Modest Mussorgsky, undated (Box 15, Item 95)
    Bach, Johann Sebastian: Concerto for Three Pianos [sic]; Myra Hess [piano] et al.; Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart: Overture to Magic Flute; Modest Mussorgsky: Night on Bald Mountain.
  - Bach, Johann Sebastian; Zoltán Kodály; Spring Choral Festival of Secondary Schools, 1965 April 20 (Box 16, Item 96)
    Bach, Johann Sebastian: Komm, Jesu, Komm; Nun ist das Heil und die Kraft; Zoltán Kodály: Psalmus Hungaricus. Spring Choral Festival of Secondary Schools. Includes musical information in storage case.
  - Bach, Johann Sebastian; Zoltán Kodály (OV-CS-1008), 1965 (Box 16, Item 97)
    Bach, Johann Sebastian: Komm, Jesu, Komm; Nun ist das Heil. Zoltán Kodály: Psalmus Hungaricus.
  - Bach, Johann Sebastian: Magnificat in D; Carissimi, Giacomo: Jepthe, 1959 November 13 (Box 16, Item 98)
    New Haven Chorale, Robert Hickok, conductor. Includes musical information in storage case.
  - Bach, Johann Sebastian: Magnificat; Carissimi, Giacomo: Jepthe, 1959 November 13 (Box 16, Item 99)
  - Bach, Johann Sebastian: Mass in B minor
    Augmented choir of St. Thomas' Church, Howard Boatwright, conductor.
    - Credo, Sanctus, and Agnus Dei, 1954 April 16 (Box 16, Item 100)
    - Kyrie and Gloria, 1954 April 16 (Box 16, Item 101)
  - Bach, Johann Sebastian: St. John Passion
    Choir of St. Thomas, Howard Boatwright, conductor.
    - Reel 1, 1963 April 9 (Box 16, Item 102)
    - Reel 2, 1963 April 9 (Box 16, Item 103)
    - Reel 3, 1963 April 9 (Box 16, Item 104)
  - Bach, Johann Sebastian: St. John Passion
    St. Thomas' Choir, Howard Boatwright, conductor.
    - Part I, 1952 April 27 (Box 16, Item 105)
    - Part II, reel 1, 1952 April 27 (Box 16, Item 106)
    - Part II, reel 2, 1952 April 27 (Box 16, Item 107)
  - Bacon/Boatwright: Songs, undated (Box 16, Item 108)
    Master copy for Cambridge CRS 1707 (stereo); 1707 AB copy. Includes technical information inside storage case.
  - Beethoven, Ludwig van: Choral Fantasy, undated (Box 16, Item 109)
    Donald Currier, piano, rehearsal tape.
  - Beethoven, Ludwig van: Eligischer Gesang, Choral Fantasy, undated (Box 16, Item 110)
    New Haven Chorale. Includes tehnical information on storage case.
  - Beethoven, Ludwig van: Mass in C, undated (Box 16, Item 111)
    New Haven Chorale.
  - Berg, Alban: Violin concerto, undated (Box 16, Item 112)
    Josef Szigeti (violin), NBC Orchestra, Dmitri Mitropoulos, conductor.
  - Billy and family: Willian Shakespeare [?], undated (Box 16, Item 113)
  - Boatwright, Helen: Various arias; Robert Schumann: Du bist wie eine Blume and Widmung, undated (Box 17, Item 114)
    Sides A and B combined on tape. Includes musical information on storage case.
  - Boatwright, Helen: A Singer's Survey of American Song
    - Reel 1, 1975 October 4 (Box 17, Item 115)
      Includes musical information on storage case.
    - Reel 2, 1975 October 4 (Box 17, Item 116)
  - Boatwright, Howard; Johannes Brahms; Dietrich Buxtehude
    Boatwright, Howard: Canticle of the Sun; Johannes Brahms: Song of Destiny [Schicksalslied]; Dietrich Buxtehude: Magnificat. Spring Choral Festival of Secondary Schools.
    - 1 of 2, 1963 April 28 (Box 17, Item 117)
    - 2 of 2, 1963 April 28 (Box 17, Item 118)
    - Reel 1 mono, OV103-A, 1963 April 28 (Box 17, Item 119)
    - Reel 2 mono, OV103-B, 1963 April 28 (Box 17, Item 120)
  - Boatwright, Howard: Music for Women of Trachis, 1955 (Box 17, Item 121)
  - Boatwright, Howard: Quintet for Clarinet and Strings, undated (Box 17, Item 122)
  - Boatwright, Howard: Serenade, Christmas Cantata, Variations for Orchestra, Trio, undated (Box 17, Item 123)
    Titles written on cardboard flap inside storage case.
  - Boatwright, Howard: Symphony, 1979 January 12 (Box 17, Item 124)
    Symphony (Stereo). Syracuse Symphony Orchestra, Christopher Keene, conductor.
  - Borden, James (OV-112)
    - Reel 1, circa 1965 (Box 17, Item 125)
      Original takes. Includes musical information in storage case.
    - Reel 2, circa 1965 (Box 17, Item 126)
      Original takes.
    - Reel 3, undated (Box 17, Item 127)
    - Side A, undated (Box 17, Item 128)
    - Side B, undated (Box 17, Item 129)
  - Brahms, Johannes: A German Requiem; Paul Hindemith: Cantata of Hope, 1958 April 19 (Box 17, Item 130)
    Yale Glee Club, Smith College Glee Club, Yale University Orchestra, Howard Boatwright, conductor. Includes musical information in storage case.
  - Britten, Benjamin: St. Nicholas (OV-CS-1005), undated
    - Reel 1 (Box 17, Item 131)
    - Reel 2 (Box 17, Item 132)
  - Britten, Benjamin: St. Nicolas; George Frederick Handel: Psalm 145 (I Will Magnify Thee)
    - 1 of 2, 1964 December 5 (Box 18, Item 133)
    - 2 of 2, 1964 December 5 (Box 18, Item 134)
    - Part I, Handel, 1964 December 5 (Box 18, Item 135)
  - Bruckner, Anton: Symphony no. 7 in E major, undated (Box 18, Item 136)
  - Buxtehude, Dietrich, undated
    - Final tape (Box 18, Item 137)
    - Copy (Box 18, Item 138)
  - Buxtehude, Dietrich: Solo and choral cantatas, 1954 May 2 (Box 18, Item 139)
    Choir of St. Thomas, Howard Boatwright, conductor. Includes musical and technical information in storage case.
  - Collegium copies [?], undated (Box 18, Item 140)
  - Consorti della musica: Rehearsal
    - Reel 1, 1973 September 29 (Box 18, Item 141)
    - Reel 2, 1973 September 29 (Box 18, Item 142)
    - Reel 3, 1973 September 29 (Box 18, Item 143)
  - Convocation 8: Organ records, undated (Box 18, Item 144)
  - Dello Joio, Norman: Various works, 1951 November 11 (Box 18, Item 145)
    Pierson College Concert. Includes musical information in storage case.
  - Divinity School Choir, 1954 (Box 18, Item 146)
    Rec. St. Thomas' Choir [?].
  - Divinity School Choir, 1954 (Box 18, Item 147)
    A copy, side B.
  - Duke's Men of Yale
    - Side A (OV-110-A), 1965 (Box 18, Item 148)
    - Side B (OV-110-B), 1965 (Box 18, Item 149)
    - Side I protection master, 1975–1976 (Box 18, Item 150)
      Song list on back cover.
    - Side II protection master, 1975–1976 (Box 18, Item 151)
  - Dupré, Marcel; César Frank; Charles-Marie Widor, undated (Box 18, Item 152)
    Dupré, Marcel: Records; includes César Frank: Pastorale, Chorale no. 3 in A minor; Charles-Marie Widor: Symphony no. 5, first movement; Symphony no. 6, first movement. Includes musical and technical information in storage case.
  - Dvořák, Antonin: Te Deum, undated (Box 19, Item 153)
  - Eisenberger, Severin (pianist)
    - Beethoven, Ludwig van: Choral Fantasy; Schubert; Wagner encores, undated (Box 19, Item 154)
    - Beethoven, Ludwig van: Piano Concerto no. 2 in B-flat, undated (Box 19, Item 155)
    - Beethoven, Ludwig van: Piano Concerto no. 5 (in E-flat), undated (Box 19, Item 156)
    - Brahms, Johannes: Piano Concerto no. 1 in D minor, undated (Box 19, Item 157)
      Cincinnati Symphony Orchestra, Eugene Goosens, conductor.
    - Grieg, Edvard: Piano Concerto in A minor, undated (Box 19, Item 158)
    - Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus: Piano Concerto no. 20, undated (Box 19, Item 159)
      Cincinnati Conservatory Orchestra, Alexander von Kreisler, conductor.
    - Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus: Piano Concerto no. 24, undated (Box 19, Item 160)
    - Schumann, Robert: Piano Concerto in A minor, undated (Box 19, Item 161)
  - English and American organists
    - Various works, 1974 December 18 (Box 19, Item 162)
    - Various works, 1946, undated (Box 19, Item 163)
  - English organists: Various works, 1931 (Box 19, Item 164)
    Includes musical information in and technical information on storage case.
  - First copies of Ives discs, undated
    - Reel 1 (Box 19, Item 165)
    - Reel 2 (Box 19, Item 166)
      Includes technical information inside storage case.
    - Reel 3 (Box 19, Item 167)
  - Frank, César; Charles Tournemire, 1930 (Box 19, Item 168)
    Frank, César: Choral no. 3; Charles Tournemire: Various works for organ. Charles Tournemire, organ. Includes musical and technical information in storage case.
  - Frank, César: Pastorale, Chorale no. 1 in E minor, Chorale no. 2 in A minor, 1957 or 1974 (Box 19, Item 169)
    Charles M. Courbolly, organ (Merc. 38A - LON). Includes musical information in storage case.
  - Handel, George Frederick: Israel in Egypt, undated
    - Sides A and B (Box 19, Item 170)
      Mono.
    - Sides C and D (Box 19, Item 171)
    - Reel 1 (Box 19, Item 172)
      Stereo.
    - Reel 2 (Box 20, Item 173)
  - Handel, George Frederick: Ode (Box 20, Item 174)
    Ode [sic: for] St. Cecilia's Day. Spring Choral Festival of Secondary Schools.
  - Handel, George Frederick; Henry Purcell, 1959 March 3
    Handel, George Frederick: Psalm 145 ("I will magnifie Thee"), Dettingen Te Deum. Henry Purcell: Psalm 79 ("Lord, how long wilt Thou be angry?"). New Haven Chorale, Donald Loach, conductor.
    - Reel 1 (Box 20, Item 175)
    - Reel 2 (Box 20, Item 176)
  - Hartt College, School of Music, undated (Box 20, Item 177)
    Various Renaissance works for voice and/or instruments. Includes musical information in storage case.
  - Haydn, Franz Josef: Creation, 1965 March 13
    - Reel 1 (Box 20, Item 178)
    - Reel 2 (Box 20, Item 179)
      Conditions Governing Access
      Pancake tape (without reel). Please contact the Music Library about access to this item.
  - Haydn, Franz Joseph: The Creation (OV-CS-1006), undated
    - Reel 1 (Box 20, Item 180)
    - Reel 2 (Box 20, Item 181)
  - Haydn, Franz Josef: Symphony no. 61, 1973 June 27 (Box 20, Item 182)
  - Hecht, Roger: Trombone recital, 1967 May 12 (Box 20, Item 183)
  - Hindemith, Paul: Das Marienleben, [Helen] Boatwright and [Paul] Ulanowsky, undated (Box 20, Item 184)
  - Hindemith, Paul: Requiem, 1956 April 15
    Yale Glee Club, Smith College Glee Club, Yale University Orchestra, Howard Boatwright, conductor.
    - Reel 1 (Box 20, Item 185)
    - Reel 2 (Box 20, Item 186)
    - Reel 3, part I: Rehearsal (Box 21, Item 187)
    - Reel 3, part II (Box 21, Item 188)
    - Performance (Box 21, Item 189)
  - Ives, Charles: Various works, 1969, undated
    - H.B. and J.K. [?], reel 1, 1969 November 2 (Box 21, Item 190)
    - H.B. and J.K. [?], reel 2, 1969 November 2 (Box 21, Item 191)
    - Symphony no. 3, undated (Box 21, Item 192)
  - Marvin, Fred: Recording sessions, 1974
    - Reel 1, 1974 November 27 (Box 21, Item 193)
    - Reel 2, 1974 November 27 (Box 21, Item 194)
    - Reel 3, 1974 November 30 (Box 21, Item 195)
    - Reel 4, 1974 November 30 (Box 21, Item 196)
  - Mendelssohn, Felix: Lobgesang (Symphony no. 2), undated (Box 21, Item 197)
  - Messner, Joseph (conductor), 1963 (Box 21, Item 198)
    Anton Bruckner Te Deum and Ludwig van Beethoven, Mass in C. Includes musical information in and on storage case.
  - Miss Hall's School (OV-111), 1965
    - Reel 1 (Box 21, Item 199)
    - Reel 2 (Box 21, Item 200)
  - Monteverdi, Claudio; Franz Josef Haydn, 1955 April 24 (Box 21, Item 201)
    Monteverdi, Claudio: Messe a Quattro Voci da Capella. Franz Josef Haydn: Missa Solemnis in B-flat major (Theresienmesse). Choir of St. Thomas, Howard Boatwright, conductor. Includes musical information in storage case.
  - Mozart Anniversary Series, 1956 March 16 (Box 21, Item 202)
    Various short vocal/choral works by Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart. Choir of St. Thomas, Howard Boatwright, conductor. Includes musical information in storage case.
  - Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus; Ralph Vaughan Williams, 1961 April 30 (Box 21, Item 203)
    Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus: Litany in B flat; Ralph Vaughan Williams: The Sons of Light. Spring Choral Festival of Secondary Schools.
  - Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus: Passacaglia, undated (Box 21, Item 204)
    m C Minor; KV 608 - def. master - LUMEN [?].
  - Mozart, Wolgang Amadeus: Requiem, 1962 December 1
    - Reel 1 (Box 21, Item 205)
      Stero.
    - Reel 2 (Box 21, Item 206)
    - Reel 1 (P4RM-2337), 1962 Dec 1 [?] (Box 22, Item 207)
    - Reel 2 (P4RM-2338), 1962 Dec 1 [?] (Box 22, Item 208)
      Includes program.
  - Mozart, Wolgang Amadeus: Symphony no. 41 "Jupiter", 1931 (Box 22, Item 209)
    Rehearsal excerpts (Blumlein stero). Sir Thomas Beecham, conductor.
  - New Haven Chorale, undated
    - Reel 1 (XTV 19231) (Box 22, Item 210)
      Master [?].
    - Reel 2 (XTV 19231) (Box 22, Item 211)
    - Reel 1 (XTV 17072) (Box 22, Item 212)
    - Reel 2 (XTV 17073) (Box 22, Item 213)
  - Orff, Carl: Carmina Burana
    - Reel 1 (Box 22, Item 214)
    - Reel 2 (Box 22, Item 215)
    - Reel 3 (Box 22, Item 216)
  - Orff, Carl: Catulli Carmina, undated (Box 22, Item 217)
  - Owen and Weinrich [?], undated (Box 22, Item 218)
  - Parisot, Aldo and Leopold Mittman: Unreleased recordings, undated (Box 22, Item 219)
  - The Perilhettes (OV-107), 1964 (Box 22, Item 220)
  - Pizarro, Dave: Organ recital, 1952 March 16 (Box 22, Item 221)
  - Porter, Quincy (F8 OP-9288), 1955 June [?] (Box 23, Item 222)
    Symphony no.1, Concerto Concertante for Two Pianos and Orchestra, and Dance in Three Time. Andre Charlin, conductor.
  - Porter, Quncy, undated
    - Quintet for Clarinet and Strings; Sextet on Slavic Themes; Sonata for French Horn and Piano; Quartet no. 3 (Box 23, Item 223)
      Includes musical information written on the inside of storage case.
    - Quaterts no. 4, 5, 7, and 8 (Box 23, Item 224)
  - Poulenc, Francis: Gloria, 1964 (Box 23, Item 225)
    Spring Choral Festival of Secondary Schools.
  - Purcell, Henry: Vocal and sacred music, 1959
    - Part 1 (Box 23, Item 226)
    - Part 2 (Box 23, Item 227)
  - Renaissance composers I, undated (Box 23, Item 228)
    Dufay, Costely, Willaert, et. al. Includes musical information in storage case.
  - Renaissance composers II, undated (Box 23, Item 229)
    Josquin des Pres and Claude le Jeune. Choir of the Protestant Church "Foyer de l'Ame," Marc Honegger, conductor. Includes musical information in storage case.
  - Rochberg, George: Songs, undated (Box 23, Item 230)
    Safety copy.
  - Rosenmüller, Johann; Johann Sebastian Bach, 1955 April 17 (Box 23, Item 231)
    Rosenmüller, Johann: Die Augen des Herren, Psalm 138; Johann Sebastian Bach: Jauchzet Gott in allen Landen, BWV 51, Christ lag in Todesbanden, BWV 4. Choir of St. Thomas, Howard Boatwright, conductor. Includes musical information in storage case.
  - Scarlatti Concert, New Haven Chorale, undated
    - Reel 1 (L8OP-4410) (Box 23, Item 232)
    - Reel 2 (L8OP-4410) (Box 23, Item 233)
  - Scarlatti, Alessandro: Selected choral works, 1960 March 25
    New Haven Chorale, Robert Hickok, conductor.
    - 1 of 2 (Box 23, Item 234)
    - 2 of 2 (Box 23, Item 235)
  - Schnabel, Arthur: Symphony no. 1 (Premiere), 1946 December 12 (Box 24, Item 236)
    Minneapolis Orchestra, Dmitri Mitropoulos, conductor. Includes musical and technical information in storage case.
  - Schoenberg, Arnold (conductor): Cadillac Symphony concert, 1934 April 7 (Box 24, Item 237)
    Conducting the New York Philhamonic, music of Mahler and Schoenberg. Recorded 1934 Apr 7, dubbed 1976. Includes musical and technical information in storage case.
  - Schola Moderna (Muse of Albertus Magnus College): French Medieval and Renaissance Music, undated (Box 24, Item 238)
  - Schubert, Franz; Francis Poulenc (OVCS 1002), 1965 May 4
    - Reel 1, Schubert: Mass in G major (Box 24, Item 239)
    - Reel 2, Poulenc: Gloria (Box 24, Item 240)
  - Schubert, Franz: Mass in G major, 1964 (Box 24, Item 241)
  - Schumann, Robert: Liederkreis, 1956 June 30 (Box 24, Item 242)
    Erich Leinsdorff, conductor.
  - Schütz, Heinrich: Christmas Cantata, 1949 December 15 (Box 24, Item 243)
    Choir of St. Thomas' Church, Howard Boatwright, conductor. Includes New Haven Symphony material and musical information in and on storage case.
  - Schütz, Heinrich: Musicalishes Exequiem, undated (Box 24, Item 244)
  - Schütz, Heinrich: Solo and choral music, 1958 March 5 (Box 24, Item 245)
    Choir of St. Thomas, Howard Boatwright, conductor. Includes musical information in storage case.
  - Select choral works, mostly Renaissance, 1960 November 18 (Box 24, Item 246)
  - Sibelius, Jean; Delius, Frederick; Tchaikovsky, Peter Ilich, 1955, undated (Box 24, Item 247)
    Sibelius, Jean: Swanwhite Suite, Royal Philharmonic, Sir Thomas Beecham, conductor. Delius, Frederick: Scenes from Irmelin, Royal Philharmonic, Sir Thomas Beecham, conductor. Tchaikovsky, Peter Ilich: Symphony no. 2, Los Angeles Philharmonic, Igor Stravinsky, conductor.
  - Sibelius, Jean: Violin Concerto, 1956 April 22 (Box 24, Item 248)
    Tossy Spivakovsky, New York Philharmonic, Dmitri Mitropoulos, conductor.
  - Spivakovsky, Jascha: Student recital, 1970 [?] (Box 24, Item 249)
    Includes music of Johann Sebastian Bach, Ludwig van Beethoven, Robert Schumann et al. Musical and technical information in and on storage case.
  - Spring Choral Festival of Secondary Schools, undated
    Music of Johann Sebastian Bach, Franz Josef Haydn, and Randall Thompson (OV-113).
    - Side A (Box 24, Item 250)
    - Side B (Box 24, Item 251)
  - Stratford Congregational Church Choir, undated (Box 24, Item 252)
  - Stratford Congregational Church Oratorio Choir, undated
    - Reel 1 (JO-8P-1902) (Box 24, Item 253)
    - Reel 2 (JO-8P-1903) (Box 24, Item 254)
  - Strauss, Richard: Death and Transfiguration (rehearsal), 1949 April 2 (Box 24, Item 255)
    Boston Symphony Orchestra, Serge Koussevistsky, conductor. Includes musical and technical information on storage case.
  - Stravinsky, Igor: Symphony of Psalms, undated
    - Box 1 (Box 25, Item 256)
    - Master [?] (Box 25, Item 257)
  - Suffield Academy (OV-102), 1963
    - The Cogs (Box 25, Item 258)
    - The Glee Club (Box 25, Item 259)
  - Sze, Yi Kwei (bass); Igor Stravinsky, undated (Box 25, Item 260)
    Sze, Yi Kwei (bass): Various vocal works; Igor Stravinsky: Pulcinella. Includes musical and technical information on storage box.
  - Tournemire, Charles (organ), undated
    - Franck, César: Cantabile and Chorale no. 3 in A minor (Box 25, Item 261)
      Includes technical information in and on storage case.
    - La Vitrome Paschali (Box 25, Item 262)
  - Trinity, final reel, undated (Box 25, Item 263)
  - Trinity Choir, 1955 April 14
    - Reel 1, side A (F8-OP-2851) (Box 25, Item 264)
    - Reel 2, side B (F8-OP-2952) (Box 25, Item 265)
  - Tunder concert, 1957 May 5 (Box 25, Item 266)
    With Helen Boatwright, soprano. Includes technical information in storage case.
  - United Church Organ, 1963 February 17 (Box 25, Item 267)
    Mary Hornberger, organist. Various works Includes musical information in storage case.
  - Vivaldi, Antonio; Randall Thompson, 1960 April 24 (Box 25, Item 268)
    Vivaldi, Antonio: Gloria; Randall Thompson: Ode to the Virginian Voyage. Spring Choral Festival of Secondary Schools. Includes musical information in storage case.
  - Westport Madrigal Singers (MO8L-0812/0813), undated (Box 25, Item 269)
  - Whiffenpoofs (H70P-3706), undated
    - Reel 1 (Box 25, Item 270)
    - Reel 2 (Box 25, Item 271)
  - Whiffenpoofs of 1964 (OV-CS-1001)
    - Reel 1 (Box 25, Item 272)
    - Reel 2 (Box 25, Item 273)
  - Whiffenpoofs: Experimental stereo [?], 1962
    - Reel 1 (Box 25, Item 274)
    - Reel 2 (Box 25, Item 275)
  - Yale Alley Cats (OV-104), 1963
    - Reel 1 (Box 26, Item 276)
    - Reel 2 (Box 26, Item 277)
  - Yale Alley Cats [of] 1965 (OV-CS-1004)
    - Reel 1 (Box 26, Item 278)
    - Reel 2 (Box 26, Item 279)
  - Yale Centennial Concert, 1954 November 5
    Howard Boatwright and Quincy Porter, conductors.
    - Reel 1 (Box 26, Item 280)
      David Stanley Smith: Prince Hal -- An Overture; Doulgass Moore: Symphony in A major. The University Orchestra.
    - Reel 2 (Box 26, Item 281)
      Charles Ives: Symphony no. 3; Quincy Porter: Concerto for Two Pianos and Orchestra. Includes musical information in storage case.
  - Yale Collection [?], undated (Box 26, Item 282)
  - Yale Collection, vol. I (OV-CS-1003), undated
    - Reel 1 (Box 26, Item 283)
      Includes music and technical information in storage case.
    - Reel 2 (Box 26, Item 284)
  - Yale Divinity School Choir, undated
    - Reel 1 (Box 26, Item 285)
    - Reel 2 (Box 26, Item 286)
  - Yale Divinity School Choir, 1953
    - Side A (XTV20195) (Box 26, Item 287)
    - Side B (XTV20196) (Box 26, Item 288)
    - Dash #1 (XTV20196-2) (Box 26, Item 289)
  - Yale Divinity School Choir, 1960
    - Reel 1 (N8OP-6513) (Box 26, Item 290)
    - Reel 2 (N8OP-6514) (Box 26, Item 291)
- Overtone and Richard C. Burns digitized and remastered recordings, Series V
  The original audiovisual materials in this collection cannot not be played onsite at Yale. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy to be made. All copies are provided as digital files. Digital transfers are conducted by third party preservation vendors that are contracted to digitize Historical Sound Recordings (HSR) collection materials. If the materials requested are already available digitally, you will be contacted with an offer to stream the recordings for 30 days, free of charge. Consult the HSR website for more information on requesting digital copies.
  - Bach, Johann Sebastian; Blake Stern; Benjamin de Laoche, 1963 April 9
    Bach, Johann Sebastian: St. John Passion; Blake Stern: Evangelist; Benjamin de Laoche: Jesus. The augmented choir of St. Thomas' Church, New Haven, Howard Boatwright, conductor.
    - Part I, original (Box 27, Item 1)
      Includes complete roster in storage case.
    - Part II, original (Box 27, Item 2)
  - Boatwright, Helen: Ives and Bacon songs, undated (Box 27, Item 3)
    Master cassette of re-masterings of Overtone no. 7 and Cambridge CRS 1707.
  - Boatwright, Howard: Various works, 1992 June 20 (Box 27, Item 4)
    Boatwright, Howard and New Haven Symphony; Yale HSR-2 first stereo version safety copy; Paul Hindemith, Violin Concerto, Joseph Fuchs, violin; Ludwig van Beethoven: Romance no. 2; Serge Prokofieff: Violin concerto no. 2, Howard Boatwright, violin; Igor Stravinsky, Pulcinella ballet suite. New Haven Symphony Orchestra, Frank Brieff, conductor.
  - Boatwright, Howard: Various works, 1967–1988
    Boatwright, Howard: Sonata for Clarinet and Piano (recorded 1988 Jan 31 [?]), Michael Webster, clarinet, Barry Snyder, piano; Twelve pieces for solo violin (recorded 1979 Feb 4 [?]), Howard Boatwright, violin; Mass S.U. singers (recorded 1967 Apr 30 [?]).